branchr.com 2010-10-26

# Branchr

## **Privacy Policy**

### We have a few principles that we always follow at Branchr.

  * We won't ask you for personal information unless we really need it, for requirements such as payment.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone, except to comply with the law, develop our products and services, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services.

### Branchr, Inc. ("Branchr") operates Branchr.com. **It is Branchr's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.**

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Branchr collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Branchr's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Branchr's visitors use its website. From time to time, Branchr may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Branchr also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Branchr, however, does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Branchr's websites choose to interact with Branchr in ways that require Branchr to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Branchr gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a website at Branchr.com to provide a last name and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Branchr – by purchasing access to Branchr's advertising service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Branchr collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Branchr. Branchr does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Branchr may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Branchr may monitor the most popular websites on the Branchr.com site. However, Branchr does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Branchr discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Branchr's behalf or to provide services available at Branchr's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Branchr's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Branchr will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Branchr discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Branchr believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Branchr, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Branchr website and have supplied your email address, Branchr may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Branchr and our products.

We primarily use our product blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Branchr takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Branchr uses cookies to help Branchr identify and track visitors, their usage of Branchr website, and their website access preferences. Branchr visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Branchr's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Branchr's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Branchr may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Branchr's sole discretion. Branchr encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Branchr.com account, you should also check your dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Attribution for this privacy policy goes to the [Automattic](http://wordpress.com/) [Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/), which is available under the [Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 2.5 Generic License.](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/)
